NEW SONGS...NEW LAUGHS...NOW ACTION....SUSPENSE...In
The Greatest Of All Roger's Hits!
The Yellow Rose of Texas is a western, action film directed by Joseph Kane.
Insurance Investigator Roy is looking for Weston and the
missing money he supposedly obtained in a robbery.
When he catches him and listens to his story, he changes his mind about him.
A freak accident locates the missing money box and they find the seal unbroken.
Roy then announces the box will be opened at the showboat that evening.
Roy Rogers, played by Roy Rogers.
Betty Weston, played by Dale Evans.
Express Agent Lucas, played by Grant Withers.
Sam Weston, played by Harry Shannon.
Captain 'Cap' Joe, played by George Cleveland.
Charley Goss, played by Weldon Heyburn.
"The Yellow Rose of Texas" is a traditional American
song dating back to at least the 1850s.
Members of the Western Writers of America chose it as one
of the Top 100 Western songs of all time.
Many versions of the song have been recorded, the most popular of
which was by Mitch Miller, whose version reached No.
1 in the United States in 1955.
Its popularity made it an unofficial state song of Texas
(the actual state song is "Texas, Our Texas").